Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers GEN MSS 996
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1896-2001; 1; 707430; 136.99 Linear Feet (550 boxes)
  - Contact Sheets, 708395
    - Reference Prints, 708396
      - Portraits, 708397
        - Simon, Ruth, 1972-1973; 708458 (Box 153)
        - Simonov, K. I. (Konstantin Ivanovich), 1965; 708457 (Box 153)
        - Sokolov, Leslie, 1989; 708456 (Box 153)
        - Soriano, Juan, 1960; 708455 (Box 153)
        - Soyer, Rafael, undated; 708454 (Box 153)
        - Spender, Stephen, 1970-1971; 708453 (Box 153)
        - Spock, Benjamin, 1969; 708452 (Box 153)
        - Stein, Jean, 1970; 708451 (Box 153)
        - Steinberg, Saul, 1959-1962; 708450 (Box 153)
        - Stern, Isaac, 1975; 708449 (Box 153)
        - Sterne, Hedda, 1978; 708448 (Box 153)
        - Stevenson, Adlai, 1961; 708447 (Box 153)
        - Stoppard, Tom, 1994; 708446 (Box 153)
        - Stout, Ruth, 1974; 708445 (Box 153)
        - Stravinsky, Igor, 1959; 708444 (Box 154)
        - Stravinsky, Vera, 1978; 708443 (Box 154)
        - Styron, William, 1966-1974; 708442; 3 Folders (Box 154)
        - Styrons, 1968-1984; 708441 (Box 154)
        - Suyin, Han, 1976; 708440 (Box 154)
        - Tang, D., 1995; 708439 (Box 154)
        - Tax, Sissi, 1994; 708438 (Box 154)
        - Taillibert, Roger, 1987; 708437 (Box 154)
        - Talbot, Augusta, 1970-1976; 708436 (Box 154)
        - Tauber, 1984; 708435 (Box 154)
        - Thacker, David, 1989; 708434 (Box 154)
        - Theatre: The Glass Menagerie, 1975; 708433 (Box 154)
        - [Thurn, Count], 1975; 708432 (Box 154)
        - Toffler, Alan, 1986; 708431 (Box 154)
        - Tolstoy, Alexandra (and Tolstoy Foundation), 1970; 708430 (Box 154)
        - Tree, Marietta, 1981; 708429 (Box 154)
        - Trotta, Margarethe von, 1988; 708428 (Box 154)
        - Tselkov, Oleg, 1979; 708427 (Box 154)
        - Untemeyer, Louis, 1967; 708426 (Box 154)
        - Updike, John, 1966-1996; 708425 (Box 154)
        - Ustinov, Peter, 1986-1987; 708424 (Box 154)
        - Vanderbilt, Gloria, 1956; 708423 (Box 154)
        - Vilato family, 1954-1986; 708422 (Box 154)
        - Voznesenskiĭ, Andreĭ, 1966-1990; 708421 (Box 155)
        - Wainer, Arcadi, 1985; 708420 (Box 155)
        - Walcott, Derek, 1995; 708419 (Box 155)
        - Wally, 1957; 708418 (Box 155)
          1957-13
        - Warhol, Andy, 1987; 708417 (Box 155)
        - Weigel, Hans, 1957; 708416 (Box 155)
        - Weinstein, Arnold, 1991; 1993; 708415; 2 Folders (Box 155)
        - Wesker, Arnold, 1990; 708414 (Box 155)
        - [Manfred], Willem?, 1992; 708413 (Box 155)
        - Wilson, Angus, 1984; 708412 (Box 155)
        - Wilson, Jane, 1965; 708411 (Box 155)
        - Wilson, Lanford, 1965; 708410 (Box 155)
        - Winger, Deborah, 1988; 708409 (Box 155)
        - Yellen, Linda, 1980; 708408 (Box 155)
          "Producer of Playing for Time"
        - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny Aleksandrovich, 1960-1990; 708407 (Box 155)
        - Zaiitsev, Vyacheslav, 1988; 708406 (Box 155)
        - Zhang, Jie, 1986-1993; 708405 (Box 155)
        - Zhavad, Mirzhavadov, 1989; 708404 (Box 155)
        - Zitman, Cornelius, undated; 708403 (Box 155)
        - Zorn, Edward, 1984; 708402 (Box 155)
        - Zuckriegl, Margit, 1991; 708401 (Box 155)
        - Empty folders A-B, undated; 708400 (Box 155)
        - Empty folders C-F, undated; 708399 (Box 156)
        - Empty folders L-V, undated; 708398 (Box 156)
  - Photographic Prints, 708031
    Photographic prints consist of more than 21,000 items, including vintage prints, exhibition/modern prints, and estate quality prints, as well as work prints, copy prints, personal photographs, and photographs by others.
    Morath did not print her own photographs. She relied on Magnum Photos and other printers to make the prints under her direction.
    Organized under nine headings: Vintage Prints, Work Prints, Exhibition/Modern Prints, Estate Prints, Subject Reference Prints, Copy Prints, Mixed Prints, Oversize Prints, and Framed Prints.
    - Vintage Prints, 708333
      Arranged sequentially by story number followed by prints with no identified story number.
      Vintage prints (approximately 5850), chiefly measuring 8 by 10 inches, made directly from the original negatives soon after their capture, usually on fiber paper. These prints usually have inscriptions by Morath and Magnum Photos staff, including captions, notes, crop marks, numbers, and ink stamps. Most of the early prints bear the photographer's name and/or copyright stamp, a title or other captioning, and the story number.
      Morath consigned a group of these prints to the Howard Greenberg Gallery in New York City for exhibition and sale around 1995, and she signed the prints at the request of the gallery for marketing purposes.
      - 1953, 708394 (Box 157)
      - 1954-01 to 1954-08, 708393 (Box 158)
      - 1954-09 to 1954-17, 708392 (Box 159)
      - 1954-18 to 1954-23, 708391 (Box 160)
      - 1954-24, 708390 (Box 161)
      - 1955-01 to 1955-07, 708389 (Box 162)
      - 1955-08 to 1955-18, 708388 (Box 163)
      - 1955-19, 708387 (Box 164)
      - 1955-21 to 1955-26, 708386 (Box 165)
      - 1955-28 to 1955-31, 708385 (Box 166)
      - 1955-32 to 1955-33, 708384 (Box 167)
      - 1955-34 to 1955-36, 708383 (Box 168)
      - 1956-01 to 1956-11, 708382 (Box 169)
      - 1956-09, 708381 (Box 170)
      - 1956-09, 708380 (Box 171)
      - 1956-10 A/C/D, 708379 (Box 172)
      - 1956-10 B, 708378 (Box 173)
      - 1956-14 to 1956-26, 708377 (Box 174)
      - 1957-01 to 1957-13, 708376 (Box 175)
      - 1957-07, 708375 (Box 176)
      - 1957-10, 708374 (Box 177)
      - 1958-01 to 1958-07, 708373 (Box 178)
      - 1958-08 to 1958-09, 708372 (Box 179)
      - 1958-10 to 1958-15, 708371 (Box 180)
      - 1958-16 to 1958-23, 708370 (Box 181)
      - 1959-01 to 1959-03, 708369 (Box 182)
      - 1959-04 to 1959-08, 708368 (Box 183)
      - 1959-09 to 1959-30, 708367 (Box 184)
      - 1959-31, 708366 (Box 185)
      - 1960-01, 708365 (Box 186)
      - 1960-02 to 1960-09, 708364 (Box 187)
      - 1960-13 to 1960-27, 708363 (Box 188)
      - 1960-16, 708362 (Box 189)
      - 1961-01 to 1961-14, 708361 (Box 190)
      - 1961-10, 708360 (Box 191)
      - 1961-11, 708359 (Box 192)
      - 1961-15 to 1961-29, 708358 (Box 193)
      - 1961-32 to 1961-52, 708357 (Box 194)
      - 1962-01 to 1962-55, 708356 (Box 195)
      - 1963-01 to 1963-32, 708355 (Box 196)
      - 1963-04, 708354 (Box 197)
      - 1963-20, 708353 (Box 198)
      - 1963-26, 708352 (Box 199)
      - 1963-26, 708351 (Box 200)
      - 1963-26, 708350 (Box 201)
      - 1963-26, 708349 (Box 202)
      - 1964-01 to 1964-06, 708348 (Box 203)
      - 1964-07 to 1964-20, 708347 (Box 204)
      - 1965-04 to 1965-23, 708346 (Box 205)
      - 1965-05, 708345 (Box 206)
      - 1965-08, 708344 (Box 207)
      - 1966, 708343 (Box 208)
      - 1967, 708342 (Box 209)
      - 1968-1969, 708341 (Box 210)
      - 1970-1972, 708340 (Box 211)
      - 1973-1974, 708339 (Box 212)
      - 1975-1979, 708338 (Box 213)
      - 1978, 708337 (Box 214)
      - 1989-1990, 708336 (Box 215)
      - "To Research" 1953-1990, 708335 (Box 216)
      - "To Research", 1953-1990; 708334 (Box 217)
    - Work Prints, 708190
      Work prints (over 6,700) represent enlargements used by Morath for editorial purposes, such as planning monographs and exhibitions. The primarily fiber paper prints measure 8 by 10 inches and 11 by 14 inches made after 1966. Many have comments and notes by Morath on versos and a few bear her signature. The material also includes some color prints.
      Notes in the guide to this group of material include represented story numbers when easily discerned by library staff.
      Arranged by subject under sixteen headings: Vintage General, China, Connecticut, Middle East, The Misfits, Nantucket, New York City, Nudes and Still Lifes, Portraits, Russia, Slovenia, Spain, Saul Stenberg, West Point, Mixed Countries, and Miscellaneous.
      - Vintage General, 708328
        - No number, undated; 708332; 4 Folders (Box 218)
        - Vintage general, 1956-1999; 708331; 37 Folders (Box 218)
        - Vintage general, 1953-1998; 708330; 16 Folders (Box 219)
        - Vintage general, 1954-1998; 708329; 28 Folders (Box 220)
      - China, 708299
        - Near Peking, 1979; 708327 (Box 220)
        - Peking-Beijing, 1978-1979; 708326; 6 Folders (Box 220)
        - Zhejiang province, 1978; 708325 (Box 221)
        - China-Asian province, 1978; 708324 (Box 221)
        - Arthur Miller in China, 1978; 708323 (Box 221)
        - China Huang Yuag Yu, 1979; 708322 (Box 221)
        - Yenan, 1978; 708321 (Box 221)
        - Guilin, 1978; 708320 (Box 221)
        - Sha Mien, 1978; 708319 (Box 221)
        - Si Chuan province, 1979; 708318 (Box 221)
        - Si Quan province, 1979; 708317 (Box 221)
        - China Fusham, 1977-1978; 708316 (Box 221)
        - Canton, 1978; 708315 (Box 221)
        - Chengou, 1979; 708314 (Box 221)
        - Shanghai, 1978; 708313 (Box 221)
        - On train, Asian Nanking, 1978; 708312 (Box 221)
        - Nanking, 1978-1979; 708311; 2 Folders (Box 221)
        - Nanniwan, 1978; 708310 (Box 221)
        - Xian, 1978; 708309 (Box 221)
        - Yangtze, 1979; 708308 (Box 222)
        - Zhongqing province, 1979; 708307; 3 Folders (Box 222)
        - China Portraits: writers and artists, 1978-1979; 708306 (Box 222)
        - Theatre, 1979; 708305; 2 Folders (Box 222)
        - Writers and artists, 1978-1979; 708304; 3 Folders (Box 222)
        - Peking, China, 1983, undated; 708303; 4 Folders (Box 223)
        - China, 1970-1979; 708302; 21 Folders (Box 223)
        - China, 1978; 708301; 14 Folders (Box 224)
        - China, 1979-1983; 708300; 28 Folders (Box 225)
          1979-05, 1983-09
      - Connecticut, 708296
        - Connecticut, 1962-1969; 708298; 25 Folders (Box 226)
        - Connecticut, 1970-1989; 708297; 34 Folders (Box 227)
      - Middle East, 708294
        - Iran, Iraq, Tunisia, 1956-1959; 708295; 30 Folders (Box 228)
          1956-09, 1959-31
      - The Misfits, 1960; 708293 (Box 229)
        1960-16, "Movie stills, Magnum Cinema and Misfits book [Fiber paper]"
      - Nantucket, 708289
        - Nantucket, 1978; 708292; 23 Folders (Box 230)
          1978-10
        - Nantucket, 1979; 708291; 5 Folders (Box 230)
          1979-03
        - Nantucket, 1974-1979; 708290; 11 Folders (Box 231)
          1974-14, 1978-10, 1979-03
      - New York City, 708286
        - Fifth Avenue, Brooklyn Bridge, Bankers Trust ads, 1958-1996; 708288; 28 Folders (Box 232)
          1958-23, 1961-03, 1961-07, 1962-52, 1970-07, 1996-16
        - New York City, 1996-1998; 708287; 14 Folders (Box 233)
          1996-16, 1997-04, 1998-03
      - Nudes and Still Lifes, 708284
        - Nudes, 1973; 708285 (Box 234)
          1973-01
      - Portraits, 708274
        - Portraits, 1954-1968; 708283; 26 Folders (Box 235)
          1954-22, 1957-01, 1958-23, 1961-03, 1965-10, 1967-12, 1968-01
        - Portraits, 1954-1999; 708282; 5 Folders (Box 235)
        - Portraits, 1954-1986; 708281; 29 Folders (Box 236)
        - Portraits, 1954-1989; 708280; 46 Folders (Box 237)
        - Portrait book (resin-coated paper), 1990-2001; 708279; 31 Folders (Box 238)
        - Portrait book (resin-coated paper), 1954-1960; 708278 (Box 239)
        - Unsigned Portraits (Fiber paper), 1953-1961; 708277; 28 Folders (Box 240)
        - Unsigned Portraits (Fiber paper), 1961-1978; 708276; 29 Folders (Box 241)
        - Unsigned Portraits (Fiber paper), 1978-1999; 708275; 26 Folders (Box 242)
          1978-10, 1979-04, 1980-08, 1982-10, 1983-03, 1983-07, 1983-09, 1986-03, 1987-24, 1988-02, 1988910, 1990-02, 1991-04, 1995-09, 1995-09, 1999-10, 1997-04, 1997-07, 1998-05, 1998-12, 1999-02
      - Russia, 708269
        - Russia, 1965-1989; 708273 (Box 243)
          1965-05, 1967-11, 1977-18, 1989-17
        - Russia, 1965-1989; 708272 (Box 244)
        - In Russia, book prints, 1965-1967; 708271 (Box 245)
        - In Russia, book prints, 708270 (Box 246)
      - Slovenia, undated; 708265
        2001-04
        - Slovenia B prints, 2001; 708268; 4 Folders (Box 247)
          Rolls 0-83
        - Slovenia B prints, 2001; 708267; 4 Folders (Box 248)
          Rolls 50-152
        - Slovenia B prints "The Border", 2001; 708266; 4 Folders (Box 249)
      - Spain, 708250
        - People, 1954-1955; 708264 (Box 250)
        - Events, 1954-1957; 708263 (Box 251)
        - Animals, 1954-1989; 708262 (Box 252)
          1954-18, 1954-24, 1955-09, 1955-10, 1955-26, 1955-31, 1955-35, 1961-32, 1989-06
        - 1950's Spain, 1954-1957; 708261 (Box 253)
          1954-18, 1955-21, 1955-26, includes Peasant Wedding in Castile, Vigo, Galicia
        - Land, cityscapes, 1954-1957; 708260 (Box 254)
        - Seville, 1987; 708259 (Box 255)
          1987-12
        - Camino de Santiago, 1998; 708258 (Box 255)
          1998-06
        - Art and Architecture, 708257 (Box 256)
          1954-18, 1954-09, 1955-30, 1956-12
        - 1950's Spain, 1954-1955; 708256 (Box 257)
          1954-18, 1955-21, 1955-26
        - La Alberca, Las Hurdes, Barcelona, Madrid, Mallorca, Northern Spain, 1954-1956; 708255 (Box 258)
          1954-18, 1955-09, 1955-10, 1956-12
        - Spain, 1954-1958; 708254; 3 Folders (Box 259)
        - Madrid, The Feria in Sevilla, Holy Week in Sevilla, 1986-1988; 708253; 2 Folders (Box 259)
          1986-08, 1987-12, 1988-06
        - Camino de Santiago, 708252 (Box 259)
        - Corrida in Barcelona, Madrid, Verbena de San Isidro, Bullfights de San Isidro, Romeria del Rocio, Vigo, Calicia, Spain, 1954-1956; 708251; 2 Folders (Box 260)
          1954-18, 1955-11, 1955-12, 1955-13, 1955-31, 1955-25
      - Steinberg, Saul, 708247; 2 Folders
        - Saul Steinberg, 1959-1980; 708249; 2 Folders (Box 260)
          1961-04, 1962-32, 1967-17, 1980-10
        - Saul Steinberg, Kentucky, 1962-1965; 708248 (Box 261)
          Steinberg: 1961-04, 1962-32; Kentucky: 1965-08
      - West Point, 2001; 708246 (Box 262)
        West Point: 2001-07
      - Mixed Countries, 708204
        - Austria/Italy, 1984; 708245 (Box 263)
          1984-13
        - Berlin, pictures of friends, undated; 708244 (Box 263)
        - Berlin, 1996; 708243 (Box 263)
          1996-03
        - "Broken Glass," New Haven, New York rehearsal pics, 1994; 708242 (Box 263)
          1994-03
        - Zoe Caldwell and Christopher Plummer, 1967; 708241 (Box 263)
          1967-09
        - France, 1955-1993; 708240 (Box 263)
          1955-21, 1958-07, 1959-10, 1993-11
        - Germany, 1996; 708239; 2 Folders (Box 263)
          1996-03, 1996-15
        - Graz, 1984-2001; 708238 (Box 263)
          1984-13, 1992-07, 2001-01
        - India, and Bharatpur, Nepal, 1993; 708237 (Box 263)
        - Iran, 708236 (Box 263)
        - Jerusalem, 1977; 708235 (Box 264)
        - Lebanon, Tehran, 1956; 708234 (Box 264)
        - Portuguese village, Lisbon, 1956; 708233 (Box 264)
        - Prague, 1994; 708232 (Box 264)
          1994-14
        - Romania, 1958-1994; 708231 (Box 264)
          1958-09, 1958-15, 1958-16, 1961-18, 1993-09, 1994-12
        - Russia, 1965-1990; 708230 (Box 264)
          1965-05, 1967-11, 1985-14, 1986-13, 1987-06, 1988-07, 1989-11, 1989-17, 1990-04
        - Russia book, 1989; 708229 (Box 264)
          1989-11
        - South Africa, 1955; 708228 (Box 265)
          1955-33
        - Thailand, 1970; 708227 (Box 265)
          1970-05
        - Tunisia, 1956-1960; 708226 (Box 265)
        - United States, 708223
          - Kentucky, 1965; 708225 (Box 265)
            1965-08
          - Los Angeles, 1987; 708224 (Box 265)
        - Vienna, 1978-1979; 708222 (Box 265)
          Vienna 1978-02, 1979-01
        - West Point, 2001; 708221 (Box 265)
          2001-07
        - Miscellaneous mixed countries, 1965-1996; 708220 (Box 265)
        - Cambodia, 1970; 708219 (Box 266)
          1970-04
        - China color conversions, undated; 708218 (Box 266)
        - Georgia, USSR, 1967-11; 708217 (Box 266)
        - Hong Kong, 1970; 708216 (Box 266)
          1970-05, 1970-06
        - Israel/Jerusalem, 1972; 708215 (Box 266)
          1972-02
        - Japan, 1970; 708214 (Box 267)
        - Portuguese village, Lisbon, mouth of Tajo River, 1956; 708213 (Box 267)
        - Thailand, 1970; 708212 (Box 267)
        - United States, 1965; 708211 (Box 267)
        - Writers and artists, 1965; 708210 (Box 267)
        - Cuba, Danube, Vienna, 1955-2000; 708209 (Box 268)
          Cuba: 1958-09, 2000-05; Danube: 1955-05, 1958-18, 1975-09; Vienna: 1975-09, 1978-02
        - Paris, China, Spain, Russia (resin-coated paper), 1955-1989; 708208 (Box 269)
          1955-09, 1955-21, 1965-05, 1967-11, 1987-06
        - Paris, China, Spain, Russia (resin-coated paper), 1955-1990; 708207 (Box 270)
          1967-11, 1986-13, 1990-04
        - Mixed countries, 1954-1993; 708206 (Box 271)
        - Miscellaneous, 1976-1993; 708205 (Box 271)
      - Miscellaneous, 708191
        - Correspondence, 1974; 1987; 708203 (Box 272)
          For preservation purposes, the prints were removed from their container. The empty container is stored in Box 279
        - "Le book", 1982; 708202 (Box 272)
        - Catherinettes, Paris, Lake Constance, Refugee Camps, Misfits, Dr. Young, 1958-1976; 708201; 6 Folders (Box 272)
          1958-19, 1959-21, 1959-25, 1960-01, 1960-16, 1976-04
        - Russia, First Issyk-Voz, The Moscow Forum, Portraits of Journalist Barbara Ungeheuer, Roxbury, 1986-1991; 708200; 23 Folders (Box 272)
          1986-13, 1987-06. 1989-20, 1991-01
        - Connecticut, William Styron, 1964-1975; 708199; 4 Folders (Box 273)
          1964-06, 1965-09, 1967-01, 1970-01, 1971-01, 1973-02, 1975-01
        - Connecticut: McCarthy Campaign, Creation of the World and Other Business, rehearsal shots, Architect I.M. Pei in Peking, 1967-1979; 708198; 3 Folders (Box 274)
          1967-01, 1968-05, 1970-01, 1971-01, 1972-06, 1974-01, 1976-01, 1979-06
        - Bankers Trust Building, Connecticut, 1963--1979; 708197; 2 Folders (Box 275)
          1963-01, 1968-01, 1975-01
        - Italy, Refugee Camps, Russia, " Timebends booktour", 1954-1987; 708196 (Box 275)
          1954-10, 1960-01, 1965-05, 1987-29
        - Russia, Kosygin at the United Nations, Venezuela, Connecticut, Takarazuka Theater and School, Japan, Twin Towers memorial, 1954-2001; 708195; 7 Folders (Box 276)
          1967-11, 1981-06, 1967-07, 1968-01, 1977-11, 1977-12, 2001-11
        - "Persia," Refugee Camps, Russia, 1956-1996; 708194 (Box 277)
          1956-09, 1960-01,1965-05, 1967-11
        - Russia, Berlin, 1965-1998; 708193 (Box 278)
          1965-05, 1967-11, 1998-14
        - Empty box, undated; 708192 (Box 279)
          For preservation purposes, the prints were removed from their container
    - Exhibition/Modern Prints, 708174
      Exhibition/Modern prints (approximately 1480), also known as Lifetime prints, represent archival quality photographic prints on fiber paper primarily 11 by 14 inches with a small group of 16 by 20 inches made by fine art printers under Morath's direction for exhibition and sale in galleries from circa 1985 until her death.
      - Exhibition/Modern Prints, 1953-1954; 708189 (Box 280)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1955-1956; 708188 (Box 281)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1957-1959; 708187 (Box 282)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1960-1961; 708186 (Box 283)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1962-1966; 708185 (Box 284)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1967-1979; 708184 (Box 285)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1980-1989; 708183 (Box 286)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1990-1995; 708182 (Box 287)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1996-1999; 708181 (Box 288)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 2000-2001; 708180 (Box 289)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1950-1955; 708179 (Box 290)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1955-1959; 708178 (Box 291)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1960s-1969; 708177 (Box 292)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1970-1990; 708176 (Box 293)
      - Exhibition/Modern prints, 1950-2002; 708175 (Box 294)
    - Estate Prints, 708170
      Estate prints (approximately 100) are high-quality prints made after Morath's death in 2002. These posthumously created prints include images that Morath did not print during her lifetime.
      It also includes 53 digital ink jet prints, 11 by 14 inches, of color photographs by Morath.
      - Estate prints, 2001; 708173 (Box 295)
      - Estate prints, 2001; 708172 (Box 296)
      - Estate prints, 2001; 708171 (Box 297)
      - Photographic The Misfits, "Arthur Miller in Paris" test prints for Inge Morath, The Road to Reno, (Göttingen: Steidl, 2006)", circa 2005; 707540; 5 Folders (Box 525)
        1960-15, 1960-16
    - Subject Reference Prints, 708140
      Arranged by subject.
      Project files represent enlargements probably used by Morath for editorial purposes, such as planning monographs and exhibitions. The primarily fiber paper prints measure 5 by 7 inches and 8 by 10 inches, with occasional prints measuring 11 by 14 inches. Many have notes by Morath on versos.
      During initial processing, library staff rehoused the following subject groups: China, Cuba, Connecticut, and New York City, as well as a portion of the Portraits.
      Notes in the guide for this group of material include represented story numbers when easily discerned by library staff.
      - China, 1978; 708169; 23 Folders (Box 298)
      - China, 1978; 708168; 26 Folders (Box 299)
      - China, 1979-1983; 708167; 43 Folders (Box 300)
        1979-5, 1979-6, 1983-4
      - China, 1983; 708166; 25 Folders (Box 301)
        1983-8, 1983-9
      - Connecticut, 1962-1964; 708165; 23 Folders (Box 301)
        1964-4, 1964-6, 1964-8
      - Connecticut, 1965-1969; 708164; 47 Folders (Box 302)
        1965-01, 1965-09, 1967-1, 1968-01, 1968-05, 1969-01,
      - Connecticut, 1970-1972; 708163; 57 Folders (Box 303)
        1970-011971-01, 1972-01
      - Connecticut, 1973-1977; 708162; 47 Folders (Box 304)
        1973-01, 1973-021974-01, 1975-01, 1977-01
      - Cuba, 2000; 708161; 19 Folders (Box 305)
        2000-05
      - New York, 1970-1997; 708160; 10 Folders (Box 305)
        1970-07, 1982-05, 1982-08, 1973-07, 1977-01,
      - New York, 1990-1997; 708159; 52 Folders (Box 306)
        1990-01, 1994-08, 1995-01, 1996-16, 1997-03, 1997-04
      - New York, 1997-2001; 708158; 25 Folders (Box 307)
        1997-04, 1998-02, 1998-03, 1999-06, 2000-01, 2000-10, 2000-11
      - Portraits, 1953-1958; 708157; 27 Folders (Box 307)
        1953-04, 1954-07, 1954-08, 1954-22, 1955-24, 1955-29, 1955-31, 1956-26, 1958-03, 1958-05, 1958-07
      - Portraits, 1958-1986; 708156; 70 Folders (Box 308)
      - Portraits, 1986-1992; 708155; 65 Folders (Box 309)
        1986-13, 1987-06, 1987-07, 1987-08, 1987-26, 1987-28, 1988-05, 1989-14, 1991-02, 1991-04, 1991-09, 1992-01
      - Portraits, 1992-1995; 708154; 36 Folders (Box 310)
      - Portraits, 1995-2001; 708153; 42 Folders (Box 311)
      - Austria, Hungary, Romania, Uruguay, 1953-1989; 708152 (Box 312)
      - United States, Danube, Regensburg, 1954-2001; 708151 (Box 313)
      - Miscellaneous Travel, 1960-2001; 708150 (Box 314)
      - Moscow, 1987-1989; 708149 (Box 315)
      - Paris, Venice, London, Saxony, 1949-1997; 708148 (Box 316)
      - Slovenia, Romania, Connecticut, 1958-2001; 708147 (Box 317)
      - Saul Steinberg, Rebecca Miller Play, Moscow, Kentucky, 1959; 708146 (Box 318)
      - Spain 50's, Romania, 1954-1958; 708145 (Box 319)
      - Spain: Camino de Santiago, Navalcán, 1954; 708144 (Box 320)
      - Spain: Pamplona, Seville, 1954-1988; 708143 (Box 321)
      - Vienna, Ireland, Italy, Dublin, Alaska, Venezuela, London, 1953-1996; 708142 (Box 322)
      - Venice, Vienna, 1955-1989; 708141 (Box 323)